So now that we've done the define stage,
现在我们完成了定义阶段
we're moving on to the diverge stage, right?
该进入发散阶段了吧？
>> The diverge stage is the next one.
下一个是发散阶段
The diverge stage is a chance for everyone to be thinking with their own
发散阶段是每个人发挥自己创造性和想像力的阶段
creativity and imagination, how should this problem be solved?
这个问题该如何解决？
>> You said solutions, so you mean more than one, right?
你之前提到过不止一个解决方案吧？
>> Yeah, we're starting to think about solutions.
是的 我们开始思考各种解决方案
Not just one.
不止一个
Everybody's thinking about many solutions.
每个人都在想很多解决方案
And then the team as a whole is thinking about whole list of solutions, and
然后整个团队一起思考这些列出的解决方案
that makes the team powerful.
那么团队的力量就会变得强大
Everyone has time individually to work on some solutions, and
每个人都有单独的时间想一些方案
as they are ready with this, then they share it with the team, and suddenly,
当方案想好时 和团队一起分享
they're looking a whole dessert tray of options for what the product could be.
突然间你会发现有这么多有关产品选项的方案
It is so exciting.
让人很兴奋
One thing that's really exciting about this stage is how quickly it can happen.
这个阶段真正让人兴奋的是它的速度
We do an exercise that's familiar to some people from Gamestorming.
我们会做一些人们熟悉的类似于游戏风暴的活动
It is called the Crazy 8's.
叫做“疯狂 8”
>> Okay, how does that go?
那是什么？
>> The Crazy 8's?
“疯狂 8”么？
You want to know?
你想知道？
Well, here goes.
是这样的
The Crazy 8's gives everyone a little piece of paper.
做“疯狂 8”活动时 每人发一张纸
And they ask the team to sketch eight ideas in five minutes.
要求团队用五分钟时间画出八个创意草图
Usually, the first reaction that people have when you ask them to sketch
通常大家第一反应就是
eight ideas in five minutes, is they think you're crazy.
“五分钟画八个创意 你疯了吧？”
And that's why we call it the Crazy 8's.
因此我们称之为“疯狂 8”
[LAUGH] >> Nice.
非常好！
>> [LAUGH] As soon as they answer this question,
当他们回答此问题时
they look at the face of the leader, and when they see that the leader is
就会看着领导 如果领导非常认真
actually serious, then they return to the writing and they start sketching.
他们就会回去开始画并勾勒草图
In five minutes, people are able to do five, six, seven, sometimes eight ideas.
五分钟时间 人们能够画出五、六、七个 有时会画出八个创意图
That allows them to warm up their mind,
用这个活动可以做头脑热身
their creative muscles are starting to flex.
使创造性肌肉活动起来
It's kind of like a warmup for a workout.
这有点类似于比赛前的热身
After that, we give the team another piece of paper and
做完后 再给团队一张纸
another five minutes and
和另外五分钟
we say from the ideas that you already have can you give me one big sketch?
然后问 从已有创意中 你能说出最佳创意是什么吗？
Label it clearly and
把它标记出来
explain what are the pieces of this layout that you're creating.
说一下你创造的东西的具体细节
Some people might be intimidated by the sketching process.
有些人害怕画图过程
This is when we remind them that we're asking them to sketch simple things.
这时我们提醒他们 只需画简单的东西
A grid that's based of rectangles, syntax labels,
像长方形网格、成列的标签
some placeholders for a pictures and icons should be.
图片占位符和图标之类的东西
With that reminder, most people are ready to re-imagine themselves
这样一提醒 人们就可以自己重新开始想像了
as the creative child that they once were.
就像小时候那个充满想像力的孩子